Guide to the Veranus A. Moore Papers, 1836-1958
Moore, Veranus A. papers, 1836-1958
- Series II. Education
  - Notebooks
    - Zoology, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Index card files - Notes and Reading Annotations, ca. 1885-1886 (Box 32)
- Series III. Correspondence
  - Ackerman, E.B. [Edward B.], 1906-1930, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Alpha Psi, 1915-1920 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1874-1926, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - American Association of Pathologists and Bacteriologists, 1906-1929, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - American Humane Association, 1908-1926 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - American Journal of Public Hygiene
  - American Legion, 1924-1926 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - American Medical Association, 1902-1929, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - American Microscopial Society, 1886-1899 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - American National Live Stock Association, 1909-1919 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - American Public Health Association, 1895-1907 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - American Public Health Association, 1908-1929, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - American Public Health Association-Rabies Speech, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - American Smelting and Refining Company, 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - American Society of Sanitary and Moral Prophylaxis, 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1898-1911 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1912-1914 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1915-1916 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - American Veterinary Medical Association, Jan-Sep1918 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - American Veterinary Medical Association, Oct-Dec1918 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - American Veterinary Medical Association, Jan-Jul 1919 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - American Veterinary Medical Association, Aug-Dec1919 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1920-1924 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1925-1931, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - American Veterinary Medical Association-International Commission on Control of Bovine Tuberculosis: See International Commission on Control of Bovine Tuberculosis
  - American Veterinary Review, 1877-1915 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Anaconda Copper Mining Company [ See also Gardiner, H.C.; Kelley, C. F.; Mathewson, E. P.; and Salmon, Daniel E. ], 1905-1911 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Association of State and Provincial Veterinary Colleges, 1911-1919 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Association of Veterinary Faculties and Examining Boards of North America, 1906-1917, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Atchison, Charles S., 1906 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Baker & McClelland Veterinary Hospital [Buffalo, NY], 1899-1927, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Baker's Veterinary Hospital [Binghamton, NY], 1906-1920 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Baker's Veterinary Hospital [Brasher's Falls, NY], 1904-1921 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Ballard, Edith: See Loeber, Edith and Maude
  - Bang, Bernhard, 1907-1911 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Bausch & Lomb, 1899-1905 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Beebe, H.S., 1907-1920 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Beebe, Verlett C., 1907-1908 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Beebe, W.L. [Minnesota], 1906-1917 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Bennett, A.B., 1898-1902 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Berns, George H., 1906-1917 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Berns Veterinary Hospital, Brooklyn, NY: See Atchison, Charles S., Berns, George H., Frink, Walter E., Gannett, Ray W., and Way, Cassius.
  - Berthier, Stella DeLiancount, ca. 1905 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - [C.] Bischoff & Co., 1904-1912, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Blauvelt, George A., 1919-1924 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Borden Company [ See also Way, Cassius ], 1901-1922 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Borden Company, 1923-1931, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Borden Company - Test Results, 1922-1923 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Boshart, C. Fred, 1908-1920 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Boynton, W.H., 1910-1924 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Briarcliff Farms [ See also New York City Department of Health ], 1902-1904 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Briarcliff Farms, 1905 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Briarcliff Farms, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Briarcliff Farms, 1907 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Briarcliff Farms, 1908 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Briarcliff Farms, 1909 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Briarcliff Farms, 1910 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Briarcliff Farms, 1911-1912 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Briarcliff Farms, 1913-1916, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Briarcliff Farms - Temperature Tests, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - British Medical Association, 1897, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Broadhurst, Jean, 1911-1929, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Brockway, A. L., 1912-1923 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Buffalo Department of Health, 1898-1917 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Burnett, Samuel H., 1906-1918, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Buxton, B.H., 1898-1900 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Carpenter, H. G., 1909-1916, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Carver, George Washington, 1911, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Cary, C.A. [Charles Allen], 1906-1927 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Central New York Veterinary Medical Association, 1910-1929 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Certified Milk Producers Association of America, 1910-1918 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Charity Organization Society of the City of New York-Committee on the Prevention of Tuberculosis, 1907-1909 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Claris, John T., 1908-1920, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Clark, C.R., 1890-1900 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Conn, Herbert W., 1907-1914 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Connaway, J.W., 1905-1927, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Cook, H.E., 1906-1920 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Cornell University
    - General, 1892-1914 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - General, 1915-1918 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - General, 1919-1921 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - General, 1922-1924 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - General, 1925-1931 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - General, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Board of Trustees [ See also Matthews, Franklin; Miller, Frank; Treman, R.H.; and Treman, Charles E.], 1906-1930, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - College of Agriculture, 1901-1908 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - College of Agriculture, 1909-1914 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - College of Agriculture, 1915-1916 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - College of Agriculture, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - College of Agriculture, 1920-1921 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - College of Agriculture, 1922-1931 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - College of Agriculture, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Agricultural Experiment Station: See New York Agricultural Experiment Station, Geneva
    - College of Veterinary Medicine
      - General, 1894-1914 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - General, 1915-1917 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - General, 1918-1923 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - General, 1924-1930 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - General, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Alumni Biographical Questionnaires, 1911 (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - Alumni Lists, 1915, ca. 1918 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Alumni Recommendations, 1915-1917 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Building Additions, 1911-1913, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Building Additions, 1919-1923 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Building Additions, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Building Additions, 1925, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Building Additions - Blueprints for Library and Incubator and Refrigerator Room, ca. 1920-1924 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Building Additions - Planning Blueprints?, ca. 1905-1925 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Expense Reports, 1922-1929 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Faculty/Staff Appointments, 1916-1919 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Glanders Correspondence, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Glanders Correspondence, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Glanders Correspondence, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Glanders Correspondence, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Library, 1901-1923, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Mailing Lists, ca. 1923-1924 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Poultry Department Correspondence, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Poultry Department Correspondence, A-E, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Poultry Department Correspondence, G-Z, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Poultry Department Correspondence, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Poultry Department Correspondence, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Prelims, 1904-1922, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Purchase Orders, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - Purchase Orders, 1925-1927 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - Rabies Correspondence, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Rabies Correspondence, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Rabies Correspondence, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Rabies Correspondence, A-V, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Rabies Correspondence, W, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Rabies Correspondence, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Reports, 1897-1909 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Reports, 1910-1913 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Reports, 1914-1916 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Reports, 1917-1923 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Reports, 1924-1931 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Reports, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Responses to Curriculum Query, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Committee on Student Affairs, 1911-1924, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Cornell Club of Ithaca, 1920-1926 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Cornell Club of New York, 1917-1931, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Cosmopolitan Club, 1914-1929, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Cornell University Christian Association, 1907-1930, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Extension Service Clipping Reports, 1924-1926 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Fraternities [Individual fraternities are filed separately], 1900-1930, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Graduate School, 1910-1928, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Library, 1903-1929 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Medical College, 1900-1911 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Medical College, 1912-1929, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Military Training/Service, 1916-1928, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - New York Agricultural Experiment Station, Geneva, 1906-1910 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - New York Agricultural Experiment Station, Geneva, 1911-1929, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - President's Office [ See also White, Andrew D. and Farrand, Livingston.], 1886-1930, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Public Health and Hygiene, 1907-1928, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Registrar, 1908-1922 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Semi-Centennial, 1915-1919 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Semi-Centennial, 1920-1921, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Treasurer and Comptroller, 1892-1922 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Treasurer and Comptroller, 1923-1929 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - War Memorial, 1927 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Cosmos Club, 1895-1931 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Cotton, Charles [ See also American Veterinary Medical Association and Government Agencies-United States-War Department/U.S. Army.], 1905-1927 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Curtice, Cooper, 1892-1917 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, 1920-1931 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Dalrymple, W.H., 1905-1922 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Dawson, Charles F., 1898-1910 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Deer Lodge Valley Farms Company: See Gardiner, Henry C.
  - DeForest, Henry, 1906-1929 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - DeVine, J.F. [ See also Government Agencies-NY-Department of Farms and Markets.], 1907-1922 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Dimock, W.W. (William Wallace), 1906-1929 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Dodge, Charles Wright, 1898-1910 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Dykstra, R. R. ( Ralph Ralph), 1909-1929 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Dyson, O.E. [ See also Illinois State Board of Live Stock Commissioners.], 1908-1915, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Eastern Live Stock Sanitary Association, 1909-1914 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Eichhorn, A, 1913-1929 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Eimer & Amend, 1907-1921 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Electropure Sales Corporation, 1923-1926 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Elmira Board of Health: See Wey, Hamilton
  - Fairfield Dairy Company [Montclair, NJ], 1914-1917, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Farrand, Livingston [ See also Cornell-President's Office.], 1905-1921 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Fenner, Casper, 1916-1922 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Fish, Pierre A., 1903-1926 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Fitch, Clifford P., 1908-1929, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Fletcher, Frank D, 1894-1912 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Flexner, Simon, 1892-1916 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Flocken, Charles D., 1901-1915 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Ford, W. W., n.d. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Francis, Mark, 1906-1922 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Freemasons, 1902-1924 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Freemasons, 1925 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Freemasons, Jan-Sep1926 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Freemasons, Oct-Dec 1926 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Freemasons, Jan-Mar 1927 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Freemasons, Apr-Dec1927 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Freemasons, 1928-1930, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Frink, Walter E., 1908-1921 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Frothingham, Langdon, 1900-1921 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Gage, Simon Henry, 1886-1929, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Gamma Alpha, 1907-1929, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Gannett, Ray W., 1906-1923 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Gardiner, Henry C. [ See also Anaconda Mining Company.], 1906-1917 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Gardiner, Henry C., 1918-1931 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Geneva [NY] Board of Health: See Harding, H. A.
  - George Washington University, 1887-1928, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Gill, Harry D., 1906-1917 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Gilliland, S. H., 1907-1915 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Giltner, Ward, 1908-1926 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Ginn & Company Publishers, 1900-1927 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Goodkind, Martin H., 1907-1931 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Goss, Leonard W., 1906-1927 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Grange, E. A. A., 1910-1917 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Grange League Federation, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Hagan, William Arthur, 1915-1929 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Hall, W. W., 1898-1908 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Hamilton, M., 2907-1921 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Harding, H.A., 1907-1925 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Haring, Clarence M., 1906-1916 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Haring, Clarence M., 1917-1928. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Hastings, E.G., 1907-1923 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Hazel, George A., 1906-1919 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Hess, E., 1911-1920 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Higgins, Charles, 1905-1924 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Hill, Hibbert Winslow, 1904-1907 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Himes, Albert J., 1892-1919 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Hoard's Dairyman, 1909-1931 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Hobasco Mason's Lodge, Ithaca: See Freemasons.
  - Hobday, Frederick T.G., 1929 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Hollingsworth, W.G., 1908-1912 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Hollingsworth, W.G., 1913-1930, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Holstein-Friesian Breeders Club of New York, 1906-1914 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Hopkins, Grant S., 1907-1920 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Hoskins, W. Horace [ See also AVMA and New York University-Veterinary College. ], 1911-1921 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Hughes, D. Arthur, 1906-1909 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Hughes, Percy M. [ See also Ithaca Board of Education.], 1898-1922 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Illinois State Board of Live Stock Commissioners [ See also Dyson, O.E.], 1907-1917 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - International Commission on Control of Bovine Tuberculosis [ See also Series V. Subject Files under same heading ], 1909-1917 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - International Commission on Control of Tuberculosis
  - International Education Board, 1925-1927 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - International Smelting and Refining Company [ See also Gardiner, Henry C.], 1914, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - International Smelting and Refining Company - Research Data, ca. 1906 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - International Smelting and Refining Company - Horse Death Data (blue print), ca. 1915 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - International Veterinary Congress, 1905, 1909 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - International Veterinary Congress, 1913-1914, 1929-1930 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Ithaca Board of Education [ See also Hughes, Percy M.], 1909-1914 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Ithaca Board of Education, 1915 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Ithaca Board of Education, 1916-1917 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Ithaca Board of Education, 1918-1919 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Ithaca Board of Education, 1920 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Ithaca Board of Education, 1921-1931 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Ithaca Board of Education, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Ithaca Board of Health, 1900-1931, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Ithaca Chamber of Commerce, 1922-1928 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Ithaca Churches, 1901-1928 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Ithaca City Government, 1908-1930, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Ithaca City Hospital, 1911-1921 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Ithaca City Hospital, 1922-1927 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Ithaca City Hospital, 1929-1931 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Ithaca City Hospital, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Ithaca Savings & Loan Association, 1916-1929, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Ithaca Tuberculosis Association, 1920-1922 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Jaynes, Cornelia, 1920-1921 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Jewell, Charles, 1906-1919 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Jordan, Edwin Oakes, 1898-1920 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Kansas City Veterinary College: See Kinsley, A.T. and Stewart, Sesco
  - Kansas State Agricultural College [ See also King, Walter E., Goss, Leonard W., and Dykstra, R.R.], 1903-1923 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Kelley, C.F. [ See also Anaconda Mining Company ], 1910-1929 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Kellog, O.U., 1906-1916 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Kelly, William H./Albany Veterinary Hospital, 1897-1908 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Kelly, William H./Albany Veterinary Hospital, 1909-1929, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Kilbourne, Fred L., 1907, 1916, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - King, Walter E., 1905-1923 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Kinsley, A.T., 1907-1922 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Klein, Louis A. [ See also American Veterinary Medical Association and Government Agencies-United States-War Department/U.S. Army ], 1909-1926 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Koenig, F. F., 1918-1920 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Lamb, J. Melvin, 1891-1898 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Law, James, 1895-1924 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Law, James-Portrait, 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Law, Walter J: See Briarcliff Farms and Government Agencies-New York-Legislature and Executive Branch
  - Liautard, Alexandre François Augustin, 1908-1918 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Linch, Charles [ See also Kelley, William H./ Albany Veterinary Hospital and Government Agencies-NY Department of Agriculture and Markets], 1906-1921, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Lipman, Jacob G., 1909-1917 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Loeber, Edith and Maude, 1903-1925, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Lowell, S. J., 1917-1920 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Lyman, Richard, 1907-1919 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Mack, Winfred B., 1906-1927 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - MacMillan Company, 1908-1917 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - MacMillan Company, 1918-1920 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - MacMillan Company, 1921-1928, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Mann, A.R.: See Cornell University-College of Agriculture and International Education Board
  - Marshall, C.J. [ See also AVMA and Government Agencies-United States-War Department/U.S. Army .], 1911-1923, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Marshall, Charles E., 1908-1916 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Martinaglia, G., 1920-1921 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Mathewson, E.P. [ See also Anaconda Mining Company.], 1913-1927 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Matthews, Franklin, 1915-1917 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Mayo, Nelson, S., 1900-1929, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - McEachran, Duncan [ See also Anaconda Mining Company and Series IV. Writings-Duncan McEachran...], 1875-1925, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - McFadyean, John, 1909, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - McLachlen Banking Corporation, 1909-1923 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - McNair, F. H., 1906-1921 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Medical Milk Commission of Essex County, New Jersey: See Fairfield Dairy Co.
  - Medical Society of the County of New York, 1907-1908 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Medical Society of the County of Tompkins: See Tompkins County Medical Society
  - Medical Society of the State of New York [ See also Series V. Subject Files-Vivisection-Medical Society of the State of New York, Committee on Experimental Medicine.], 1901-1927 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Merck, 1907-1929 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Meridale Farms, 1906-1910 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Merillat, Louis A. (Louis Adolph), 1868-, 1907-1911, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, 1921-1930 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Metzger, H. J., 1919-1921 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Meyer, Karl Friedrich, 1910-1927 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Microscopial Society of Washington, 1891-1892 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Milbank Memorial Fund, 1923-1924 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Milbank Memorial Fund, 1925-1927 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Milbank Memorial Fund, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Milbank Memorial Fund, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Milbank Memorial Fund, 1930-1931, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Milks, Howard Jay, 1888-1923 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Miller, Frank, 1911-1929, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Mitchell, J. F., 1915-1917 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Mohler, John Robbins: See Government Agencies-US-Bureau of Animal Industry
  - Moore Family: See Series VII. Family Papers
  - More, Warren D., 1890-1930, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Morris, Claude D., 1902-1911 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - [H.K.] Mulford Co. [ See also Reichel, John.], 1906-1930 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Munce, T. E., 1918-1924 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Munce, T. E., 1922-1927 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - National Association Bureau of Animal Industry Employees, 1913-1927, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - National Association for the Study and Prevention of Tuberculosis, 1904-1915 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - National Consumers' League, 1907-1908 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - National Tuberculosis Association, 1919-1928, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - [Thomas] Nelson and Sons, 1910-1928 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Nesbitt, Edward J., 1906-1920 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - New York Association for Improving the Condition of the Poor, 1907-1914 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - New York City Department of Health, 1907-1929 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - New York City Municipal Civil Service Commission, 1915-1916 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - New York State Agricultural Society, 1916-1924 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - New York State Association of Dairy and Milk Inspectors, 1928-1929 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - New York State Association of Public Health Laboratories, 1922-1930 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - New York State Breeders Association, 1908-1925 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - New York State Commission for the Investigation of Bovine Tuberculosis, 1915-1916 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - New York State Dairymen's Association, 1906-1928 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - New York State Guernsey Breeders Association, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - New York State School of Agriculture at Alfred University, 1910-1921 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - New York State Veterinary Medical Society, 1898-1929, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - New York State Veterinary Medical Society - Moore Retirement Party, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - New York University-Veterinary College [ See also Hoskins, W. Horace and Series VI. Ephemera - New York University.], 1915-1922, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Niver, Edwin, 1892-1909 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Nodyne, E. H., 1906-1910 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Nu Sigma Nu, 1907-1926, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Olafson, Peter, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Osler, William, 1893, 1900, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Park, William Hallock: See New York City Department of Health
  - Parke, Davis, & Co. [ See also King, Walter E.], 1906-1924, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Pasteur Institute, 1907-1921 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Peabody, James E., 1908-1911 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Pearson, Leonard, 1900-1909 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Pearson, Raymond A. [ See also Government Agencies-NY-Dept of Agriculture and Markets and Cornell College of Agriculture], 1912-1917, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Pease, H. D. [ See also Government Agencies-NY-Dept of Health.], 1909-1914 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Phi Kappa Phi, 1920-1929, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Phi Sigma Kappa, 1899-1928, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Pickens, E. M., 1914-1930, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Prescott, Samuel Cate, 1910-1926 (Box 10, Folder 41)